The movie, ZENBU OF TOKYO, is being broadcast live on the 7 cities tour live broadcast live.
It has started. Nice to meet you.
Good evening, everyone. I'm Kumi Sasaki of Hinata Zaka 46.
Please.
And...
Can you see me?
I'm Nao Kosaka. Nice to meet you.
I'm Haruyo Yamaguchi. Nice to meet you.
Today, October 25th, Friday, is the release day of the movie,
which all four of us will be in.
Congratulations!
And today, we have 10 students from all over the country,
including Rina Watanabe, who is a graduate student,
to greet the audience.
Everyone is going all over the country.
This is what it looks like when you say who's going where.
Really, there are a lot of people going around.
There are also members who are going to the countryside.
That's right.
KAMORIN and HARUHARU.
KONISHI.
KONISHI too.
KIRARI-CHAN too.
They're going like this.
That's good.
That's right.
Everyone is going, so we, the senior members, will do a live stream with the four of us to make the movie of Tokyo more exciting.
Today, we will be connecting with a certain member during the stage greeting, and we will be sharing our experiences of traveling to school with the four of us,
and we will be sharing our experiences of traveling to school with the four of us, so please enjoy the live stream together.
We don't know what kind of report this is, so we don't know at all.
We are the teachers who stayed in Tokyo.
The teachers who stayed?
Hario sensei.
Please call me Hario sensei.
Hario sensei and Kosaka sensei.
I'm the head of the school.
Oh, the head of the school!
The head of the school!
I'm the head of the school.
Wow.
As expected.
That's too casual.
I just said it.
I hope you enjoy it too!
Let's talk about the movie, ZENBU OF TOKYO.
The director, Yoko Chougenji, plays the role of the leader, Ikezono.
She has a perfect schedule for Tokyo during her school trip.
She is looking forward to traveling with the same group of members.
The day of free action awaits her.
She thinks, what? A multi-verse? A reincarnation of another world?
She tries to resolve her plan and heads off to Tokyo.
In fact, her wish and her feelings for her ex-boyfriend are hidden.
Each of the members of the group came to Tokyo with their own thoughts.
This is a roller coaster movie where the 11 girls of Hinatazaka 46 experience the first day of their teenage years as high school girls.
We're on the roller coaster.
I got the wrong car.
I explained it in my mouth, but of course, we have a trailer for the trailer, so please take a look.
Please.
We're going to go to Tokyo!
A school trip to Tokyo.
Let's enjoy all the Tokyo-like places!
The class president has a perfect plan.
Let's meet at 12 o'clock, okay?
Okay!
What?
That's fast.
What? What's going on? Everyone's not here.
Everyone's here.
No, it's not. It's a parallel world.
11 people who have been separated.
Megwin, what are you doing here?
I don't want to be with Moriya.
Everyone!
I'll definitely get a T-shirt limited to 4 stores.
I'm passing through the cool system from Tokyo.
I'm a friend when I was here.
Wow, you're from Tokyo.
I'm taking an audition.
I'm an idol.
You were on your way to school, right?
What was that about?
I thought it was fate.
I think Chisa-chan is coming this way.
Chisa-chan! Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
What happened?
I...
I'll ask everyone in the class to help me.
What are you doing?
11 girls who are busy on their way to school.
Jet Coaster Movie
What is that?
Everyone in Tokyo was there.
Jet Coaster Movie
Yay!
It's a movie like this.
We've already seen it before, but it's really like a roller coaster.
It was a roller coaster. The development is really fast.
The four-seater really changes the scene a lot, so it's always fun.
There are a lot of places in Tokyo.
Yes, there are.
Here.
As expected.
I've been here.
I've been to Sky Tree.
Sky Tree.
It was shown in the video.
What is it?
We are.
Oh, that's right.
Really?
Actually, it was during the event.
It was shown in the video.
There were such things.
Yes.
It was.
Amazing.
So,
I would like to explain again what kind of role each member has in the movie and what kind of relationship they have.
Please.
Nao-chan, please.
Yes.
Are you connected?
It's still a bit far.
Do you hear something?
I hear something.
Hello.
Kaho-rin?
Kaho-rin!
Wow!
Amazing!
I'm at the movie theater.
Wow!
You guys are amazing!
You guys suddenly connected.
I was surprised.
I want to show you the movie theater in Hokkaido.
I want to see it.
Please make it cute.
I'm saying something.
Kaho-rin.
Kaho-rin, I love you.
I want you to show me Hokkaido.
I want to see it.
I'm happy.
It's a hand.
Wow!
Hello.
Ario-chan.
Wow!
There are a lot of people.
Thank you so much for coming to Hokkaido!
Thank you to everyone who came to Hokkaido!
How was it?
Hokkaido was really warm and...
The rice is delicious too.
That's nice.
It's our hometown.
That's right.
How was it? After the stage greeting?
We were in the middle of the stage greeting.
Oh, I see.
We were in the question section.
Oh, the question section.
I see.
That's nice.
Have you guys watched the movie?
Have you guys watched it?
We've watched it.
There are many people watching it.
It's a mess.
I think we're having a social meeting without a platform.
I don't feel like we're having a stage meeting.
We're friends.
It was so warm.
It was good.
Did you enjoy the movie?
Yes, we did.
That's good.
Yay!
So cute!
Masakado-san said it was cute.
Thank you.
I'm Alirin.
That was a word from Alirin.
Megu-chan was cute too.
Thank you.
She was cute.
She had a strong personality.
Will you show us your report later?
Yes, I will.
I will be leaving for Hokkaido later.
Please look forward to the report.
Thank you.
We have this and that.
I'm happy.
This is all live streaming.
Yes.
I think there are comments.
Kaho-rin.
Kaho-rin is cute.
Thank you.
It's rare.
It's rare, isn't it?
I'm about to call.
Excuse me.
I'm calling you for a long time.
Did you have anything to say?
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
You are free.
It's my pace.
It's a must-have item.
Thank you for the live broadcast.
Good luck.
I'm going to the floor.
Amazing.
It was like a cat's eye.
It was funny.
It was a very warm stage.
It was warm.
It was at home.
Is everyone at my pace?
Like Kaorin.
Like Hokkaido.
Everyone said something they left behind.
The broadcast will be connected like this, so please don't miss it.
We talked about the total number of people.
Please show us the total number of people.
Like this.
Can you see it?
This is the leader of the Ikezono.
The same group as Ikezono is here.
Kiri Chisa-chan
And Megu-chan
And below that, Ayano-chan
And Setta Shiori-chan
These 5 are the Ikedonohan
We're going on a school trip together.
But there are other members around us.
But these five members are separated.
They're the ones who are living apart.
This is like a side of the story.
I want to get a character I like.
A Tokyo-only character.
They're all like, what do you want?
And then?
Let's go over here.
Yes.
Where's Mastani-san?
Mastani-san is...
This Mitsutake Yumeka-chan is...
She's Mastani-san's friend when she was in Tokyo.
Mastani-san moved from Tokyo, right?
Yes.
And when she came to Tokyo for a school trip, she happened to run into her.
And Hanasato-san is like Masutani-san's favorite.
She's the one I admire.
Like a person from Tokyo.
Like cool.
Nagano, right? Nagano's school.
Yes, Nagano's school is the stage.
And then, what about Megu-chan?
There was a trailer for Moriya-kun.
Moriya-kun?
Oh, she's here again.
What happened?
I can hear you!
Are you from Fukuoka?
Yes, I am!
Wow!
It's close!
It's a movie theater!
I can hear you!
It's like a live show!
How was it?
Yes, we are really excited.
That's nice.
She is laughing.
We are doing our best to watch a lot of ZENBORG TOKYO.
Great!
Great, Sumire!
Tama-chan and Sumire are great too
The two of them are in the same group
So you two met to buy some goods together?
Yes, that's right.
Did anyone else come to see the show?
We just met before the show.
Oh, I see.
I was a little bit sleepy.
She's in a business relationship.
It's being broadcasted live on YouTube.
It's surprisingly far.
The physical distance is long.
I can hear everyone's voice.
Thank you.
What are you talking about?
Right now, Shiori Shitta's character, Tamaki, is asking who looks best in a four-member group.
That's a very exciting topic.
It's also at home.
It's very at home.
I'm really excited.
By the way, who did you choose?
I chose Mitsuki Jiraoka.
She's on the show.
Who decided that?
Me.
Not everyone.
Everyone is watching.
I was told to come here.
Tomo-chan came here on her own.
Do you want to wear something?
Yes, I want to.
Who looks best in glasses?
You can say it all at once.
Among these three?
She's smart.
Among these three, who looks best in glasses?
I'm sorry.
I think it's in the water
Everyone is in the water!
Absolutely
I can't hear
I'm glad you can't hear
Everyone is in the water!
Thank you
Everyone, please say something.
Nami-san! Nao-san! Kana-san!
Thank you!
Thank you, Fukuoka people!
Thank you.
You two will send us your school trip reports right?
Yes, we will send you our reports.
We are looking forward to it.
Yeah, then, please promote the movie to everyone in Fukuoka.
Yes, thank you.
I'll do my best!
Please enjoy it!
Thank you, see you again!
Thank you very much.
It's like the end of a phone call.
But this time it ended properly.
It ended properly.
I couldn't get used to it.
Let's go to the next question.
It really comes suddenly.
Where was it?
Moriya was talking about it.
I was talking about Moriya.
What did you focus on?
The relationship between these two is...
What is it?
It's a long question.
It was fun, wasn't it?
I really liked this group.
Kirari-chan's role was unexpected.
From the moment she came out, she was too strong.
Kirari-chan's character was in the next day.
I could only see it.
It's amazing.
It's only Mio.
Mio was completely covered.
That's good.
But Kaori's face and expression change a lot, but they're all cute.
I know.
I thought that was amazing.
Her expression was so cute.
It was so cute.
She never made the same expression.
She's the same when she's looking at Moriya and when she's talking to Mio.
You can see a lot of different sides of her.
She's the first person I've seen with such a cute face.
She's so charming.
And then, Chisa-chan.
After we split up, I wonder what she'll do.
Oh, oh, oh!
What? What?
In the back.
Chisa-chan's...
She went to audition for an idol.
And the person who gave her the opportunity to audition was...
Rin Arikawa, who is here.
I played her.
Yes.
Rin Arikawa gave her courage.
And she wanted to audition for her.
Because it's in the smartphone case.
Yes, I drew her autograph.
So you actually drew this as Nao-chan's autograph?
Yes.
It's my own room.
I drew it.
Chisa-chan takes good care of it.
We got separated, but we kept up with our schedules.
We were so happy.
But...
No...
I didn't know I could go in such a short time.
Is this really possible?
But...
I just had to go.
I was really nervous.
After this kind of school trip,
How many hours did you have to re- gather?
I was there for about a day.
So you're free for the whole day?
Yes.
I think that's a good time.
I'm free until the evening.
Then you can go.
It's probably 8 o'clock.
That's right.
8 o'clock doesn't seem like a lot of work.
You just have to take pictures.
That's right.
I think it's J.
J? What's J?
MBTI
What's J?
P and J
P is not planned, J is planned
It's definitely J
It's definitely MBTI J
I want to hear everyone's MBTI
The characters were pretty strong
It was amazing
This is also J
But it's just that Settachan is J, so it might be different
Ah, that's true
There's a scene like that
There was
It's like everyone's talking
It's dangerous, there are people who haven't seen it
That's right
But I hope you feel like you want to see it
But the teacher was really good, wasn't he?
No, it was really good
Hinuken
Hinuken?
It's Hinuken
It was called Hinuken
Hinuna Kenji, so it's Hinuken
A little
I thought it was Himu-ken.
Himura-san.
I thought it was Himura-san a little bit more.
Hinuken.
It was really good.
It was the best.
It was amazing.
I thought, there's a teacher like this.
There's definitely a teacher like this.
There is.
I didn't like it.
I remembered.
Kumi-san's project when she was a student.
I thought, there was a teacher like Hinuken.
I didn't like it.
And this.
Yes, taxi driver.
You're holding the key, aren't you?
I'm holding the key.
I thought, I'm involved in this kind of thing.
In this lineup, taxi driver?
I thought a lot about it.
How do you get involved?
I wonder if this is involved.
That's what it is.
The foreshadowing was amazing.
No, it was amazing.
That's right.
That's how it is.
We can talk about it all we want.
But it's not like we're going to say it.
We're going to be a bit of a spoiler.
So, we have a report from one of the members.
Let's take a look.
Where am I right now?
Where is it?
Here.
It's here!
Kumi-san, Nao-san, Hario-san, good evening! I'm Haruka Yamashita.
I'm in Aichi Prefecture, my hometown.
Here you can see Nagoya Castle.
It's been lighted up.
And on top of that is the Shachihoko.
I've also been to the Shachihoko.
I see.
Please try it!
I'm excited.
I'll talk while putting it on my head.
I'm from Aichi Prefecture, but please listen to the voice of insects.
It's a place with so much nature.
Every time I come here, I get really excited and excited.
Please come here.
There are many recommended places for school trips.
This is my report on school trips.
I will go to the stage.
Thank you.
I received a report from HARUHARU who is in AICHI.
I was hungry.
I don't feel like I'm a president.
But Haruharu was doing it for me.
You were a president.
I'm looking forward to receiving the 4th grade students from now on.
You said you were going on a school trip.
Where did you go on a school trip?
I went to middle school in Nara, Osaka.
You're going to Osaka?
Yes.
Where did you go?
I went to Nagasaki when I was in middle school.
What?
Oh, that's where you went?
Yes, that's where.
You're going to the west more and more.
I'm going to go up.
Is it Tokyo?
Where did you go?
I went to Kyonara in middle school.
What?
Kyonara?
Kyonara.
Oh, Kyonara.
What's that?
What's Kyonara?
Everyone in middle school is Kyonara.
Kyonara and Hida.
That's the name of the school.
We're from Kyoto.
Oh, I see.
But we didn't go to Osaka.
Really?
Did you go there?
Yes, we did.
What?
Really?
We went there for a day.
What?
That's the best school.
We went there.
Wow.
That's amazing.
I think I stayed there for one night.
Oh, really?
I don't think so.
I stayed there for two nights.
I stayed in the high school from Hiroshima to Nagasaki for 4 nights and 5 days.
Wow! That's amazing.
I went to Hiroshima by the same bus.
I went to elementary school in Hiroshima.
Oh, really?
Yes, I stayed there for one night.
Elementary school?
Do you remember?
I remember.
I said Niko.
Niko.
This is...
Isaru?
Iwazaru?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I'll look it up later.
It's a good place.
I went to a elementary school in Mie.
Mie?
In Shima Spain Village.
I know.
I've heard of it.
It's quite different.
This is fun.
I want to hear it from all the members.
All of the members of the school trip of Tokyo.
Please try it.
Next is the goods unboxing corner.
I was looking forward to it.
To commemorate the release of the movie, we have official goods and a pamphlet for the theater.
From today, the official goods and the pamphlet will be sold at the theater and online store.
We have prepared it here today.
Thank you.
Which one?
Let's go with the pamphlet first.
This is the pamphlet.
It's cute.
Even if you put it in your room.
It looks good.
It's cute.
We can't show you the inside, but...
Like this.
Can we see it?
It's cute!
It's so good!
I want to protect it.
It's so cute! It's shiny and shiny.
There's one each.
Wow, this kind of interview is also...
I'm grateful. There's a profile too.
Nice, nice.
It's a one-person interview.
Huh?
There's one.
There's a photo too. Thank you.
This one!
This is good.
This one...
Everyone in the sun can see it.
You can see it in the sun.
This is really good.
This is good.
There is a school.
This school is nostalgic.
Is that so?
What school did you go to?
It was a school used in a drama.
It was the same school.
There is a story behind it.
This is the end of the video.
We are going to have a lot of fun.
There are many things that we can only find here.
This is a must.
Do you have any?
Which one?
There are many random ones.
Let's go.
Shall we?
Shall we go to the drug store?
Yes.
This is a mini photobromide card.
There are a lot of them.
I'll open it.
I'll draw one at a time.
Is that okay?
Do that.
Randomly.
Then I'll take this.
OK.
Who will open it?
Mini photobromide card.
I'll go at once.
I'm nervous about this.
Ready, go.
Ta-da.
It's a mini photobromide card.
Settachan! Masutani-san.
It's cute. I'm Masutani-moshi.
Oh, it's Mi-chan. Cute.
Mitsutake-san. This is good.
This is really good. It's a size that can be put on your phone.
This picture is that, right?
Yes, the illustration drawn here is the illustration drawn by Shogenji Yoko.
That's right. That's right.
It's really good.
The color is also very good. This is a decorated Neme Koto.
This is really good. Please get this.
I'll go more.
I'm curious about that.
This is an acrylic key holder. I love key holders.
I'll try this too.
Let's do it.
This one.
Acrylic key holder.
It's pretty big.
The random goods are
4-person plus me.
Oh, there's a person.
There's a person.
I'm interested.
This is today's entry.
Here we go.
Ready, go.
Ta-da.
It's like this.
Amazing.
cute!
Meg-chan!
Tsuchan!
Oh, Alirin!
Wow!
Alirin!
It's not a Tsuchan!
Cute!
It's amazing!
There is also a picture of Yoko.
This is really good!
All of Tokyo is also drawn.
I want this one.
Isn't this one nice?
This one is really nice.
I'm really thankful for this one.
I'm so happy.
I want to put this on my hair.
I want to put it on my hair.
This is nice.
I recommend this one.
I'll exchange it.
You're so kind.
I can do that.
This is nice.
The size is also very good.
Shall we go further?
Next is the pen and key holder.
There are many key holders.
I like key holders, so I'm happy.
Then I'll put it on this.
It's easy to open.
We'll start immediately.
What is this?
It's like a flag.
Ready, go!
Oh, it's a flag!
Wait!
I'm a little surprised.
What?
Isn't it amazing?
It's fate.
It's a color.
Isn't it amazing?
It's the second time.
It's a second time.
This shape is so cute.
The color is cute.
What's wrong?
I'm sleepy.
I thought it was a triangle.
It's good.
It's a triangle that looks like it's going to be in the math.
Oh, shoes.
Finished.
Oh, well, it's like this.
There's more.
I want to introduce you to a lot of things.
There was also AXTA.
Can't you show me that?
A student's notebook.
Student notebook.
Isn't this really good?
This is...
Both of them are notes?
Mini notebook and notebook.
Student notebook notebook.
I took a lot of notes.
It's rare.
I've been confused.
It's cute.
You can use it.
There's a lot of stuff.
It's cute.
Please check it out.
If we have time later,
Let's do it again.
Please.
Here's another report from the members.
I'll introduce you to some of them.
Please.
First of all,
we have a live streamer here.
Let's start with Kaholyn.
Welcome to Hokkaido.
I'm in Fujishima, Hokkaido.
I'm going to eat
a Chinese can.
Ta-da!
Looks good!
Let's eat.
Looks good.
There are a lot of vegetables.
I'm a Zingisukan fan, so I'm going to eat Zingisukan rice bowl.
Please wait a minute.
I'll enjoy having this.
I'll eat rice and meat first.
This is...
Umarin Kourin
This background is also cute.
I was able to draw it.
It's love.
Hokkaido love.
After all,
I'm a sheep, too.
I'm a sheep.
It's delicious.
I'm a sheep from Hokkaido.
Sheep.
She's cute.
I'm okay with this.
Oh, that's good.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I was so happy.
It's really good.
It's like a welcome board.
That's right.
That was amazing.
It's warm.
When you go to Hokkaido, you can eat Genghis Khan.
That's right.
Hokkaido is a great school trip.
It's really good.
Is there a place to go to Hokkaido?
I think there is.
Why do you look it up?
I don't know.
But I'm sure there is a place to go.
But there are many high school students in Hokkaido.
Is that so?
I don't know about high school.
I think it's Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
But I think there are many people in Hokkaido.
Maybe there are many people in Hokkaido.
I think so.
Is there anyone who has been there?
Have you been there?
Yes, I have.
Skiing?
Winter sports?
Yes, yes.
It was a high school in Hokkaido.
There's something like that.
It looks fun.
Going on a school trip is fun.
Really.
Let's go on a school trip with your friends.
I want to go!
Skiing and snowboarding.
I want to do a bonfire.
That's great.
That's a great idea.
Let's do it.
There's a report video.
Please watch it.
Kumi-san, Nao-san, Haruyo-san, good evening.
We are now in Kobe.
It's so beautiful.
The port.
We are in Kobe.
Here is the red and blue lights.
Today, there are many people here.
It's crowded.
Many people.
We are going to say hello to the stage.
We are going to enjoy it.
It's very crowded.
It was a video.
Have you ever ridden a motorcycle?
Yes, I have.
I rode it once.
Yay!
It's a wonderful place.
It's nice.
Kobe is nice.
I want to go to Kobe.
Why did you come out of nowhere?
I thought it was cute, I thought it was cute.
I made a mistake.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm in the middle of the video.
I made a mistake.
I thought it was cute.
It's nice.
It's a very big city.
Yes.
It looks like it.
Even though it's next to us, it's Tottori.
Is that so?
Tottori is next to Hyogo.
With Hyogo?
Yes.
This part is tight.
It's tight.
Actually.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
It's so different.
Kobe is nice.
It's a city in the middle of nature.
I see.
I could go there right away.
I wanted to stay there.
There are many nice hotels.
Did you go to Higari?
There are many.
What did you do?
I went to Awaji Island.
The onion island?
Yes.
You can go from Kobe.
It's so nice.
I like it. And those two were calm.
I was a little slow.
I've been on the screen.
I didn't expect to be on the screen in a remote video.
There's no such thing.
There are only two of us.
It's good.
I'm looking forward to it.
And then there's more.
Please.
KUMI-SAN!
NAN-SAN!
HARUYO-SAN!
The stage interview has just ended!
I'm Tamaki Ishizuka, playing the role of SETASHIORI.
I'm Sumire Miyachi, playing the role of Akane Yonatori.
I was nervous.
I was nervous. It's my first time doing a stage interview.
And it's Fukuoka, so I had a lot of fun with everyone from Fukuoka.
Thank you very much.
And today...
We will be delivering our school trip report to you.
Here it is.
Ready, set, go!
Our school trip report is...
Hakata's One Bite Dumplings!
I'm so happy!
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
Looks delicious.
How is it?
Umatama-nyan!
Umatama-nyan is here!
Is it delicious?
It's good.
I'll try it too.
Itadakimasu.
Looks delicious.
I'll have a bite.
This is a little...
I came here with you guys, so I thought it would be nice to give you a present.
Sure, you can give me a present.
Just for today.
I won't give you.
Thank you.
You won't give me?
Cute.
I'm jealous.
I'm glad you like it.
Thank you.
Bye.
It's a very unique report.
I'm sorry.
After they all understood what gyoza was, they all started drinking it.
Gyoza?
They all like gyoza.
They started drinking it.
It looks so good.
It's good.
I didn't know there was such a gyoza in Fukuoka.
I didn't know.
It's a bite-sized gyoza.
It looks like it's easy to eat.
It's really good.
It's good.
I wonder if there is such a thing in Fukuoka, too.
On a school trip.
There is.
I wonder if there is.
Fukuoka.
Is there?
I'll ask you everything.
Is there anything you've been to in Fukuoka?
Nagasaki is a classic, so I've been there.
That's true.
I wonder if I'll go.
I've been to Nagasaki for a peace study or something.
I've been there, too.
I wonder if I'll go.
It's famous.
Everyone is saying that there is Gyoza Nanjyu.
I went to Fukuoka.
It looks fun.
I heard that Fukuoka is a middle school.
The food is delicious.
That's right.
I'm jealous.
I've only been to Fukuoka on tour.
I want to go there in private.
Can you go to Fukuoka on a day trip?
Really?
I've been there.
It's a lot of fun.
I wonder if so.
I'm not embarrassed.
It's not something to be embarrassed about.
We were just talking.
I thought you were complimenting me.
I'm from Nagasaki, Fukuoka.
I see.
That's great.
In all of Tokyo,
there are some troubles during school trips.
There are some troubles during school trips.
There were such things.
For me,
I went to Osaka.
I went to the place.
I've never been on a roller coaster before.
I was on a roller coaster with a friend.
It was a big one.
The one at the entrance.
It was the scariest one.
I was so scared.
There was a picture of me on it.
I was on a graduation album.
I was so scared.
I saw it.
It's cute!
Like that.
After crying?
After crying or before getting on the train.
You don't like it anymore.
Cute!
I'm back to being a social worker.
I don't like it.
So, the classmates can see that face.
They can see it.
That's nice.
That's cute.
It's a cute happening.
That's nice.
You remember that kind of thing, right?
I remember it.
Really.
Do you have it?
It's not a happening, but it's a scene that I'll never forget.
I had a lot of classes in high school.
There were about 12 classes.
So I couldn't go at once because there were too many people.
There were about 500 people.
I couldn't go, so I was in the first half and second half.
I followed the same route from the opposite side.
It was fun!
The first day we went to the first class, I was in the first half.
The second half class was the last class.
We arrived in Hiroshima and went home from Nagasaki.
The second half class was to go back to Nagasaki and go home from Hiroshima.
That's amazing!
That was the plan.
We really followed the plan.
The bus guide said on the highway,
I'll take you to the second half class from now on.
I was surprised.
It was a big event.
I was stuck in the window.
I was not allowed to talk to my friends.
I couldn't contact them.
I was so scared.
I thought I was going to be a friend.
But I was in a hurry.
I couldn't see anything.
The only thing I could see was a really strict teacher.
I could only see her hands.
I couldn't see anything.
I was so scared.
I can never forget that moment.
We were all like...
We passed each other 6 times and it was over.
It was so much fun.
It was so fun.
That's nice.
Were you in high school?
Yes.
Around the second year of high school.
It was so cute.
We were all like that.
We went to the restaurant where the second half class was.
It was like a multi-verse.
It was a dirty school trip.
If there are many people, we go to different places.
We had such a system.
It's new.
That system was super fun.
That's good.
I can't forget the highway.
Oh, here it is!
Yoko!
Wow, there's a lot!
I can hear you!
There are so many people
I can hear you
I'm glad
Oh!
She answered back
How was the stage greeting?
Are you excited?
Oh, she's excited.
She's excited.
Yay!
That's good.
Oh, I see.
Yoko is...
Is it Osaka?
Hyogo.
Yoko is not Hyogo!
Yoko is Osaka!
Wait a minute!
Really?
I thought it was a new technique.
What?
Welcome to Osaka!
I just remembered.
Thank you very much.
Did you say welcome back?
Can I do it now?
I'm home.
Did you say that?
I think I said a lot and I didn't get it all.
Maybe.
But everyone is saying welcome back.
That's amazing.
That's nice. What did you talk about?
I'm going to do a question corner now.
I've just started watching it.
She's just started watching it.
Have you all watched the movie?
I heard you're going to watch it from now on.
It's fun. You're doing a great job.
Yes!
She's full of energy.
I think we should go back to the stage.
We're going to enjoy the stage performance in Osaka.
We're looking forward to it.
We're waiting for the report.
Thank you.
Oh!
I'm sorry, but I'm from Osaka.
I'm from Hyogo.
That's why I'm saying that I'm from Hyogo and I'm going to Osaka today.
I was really impatient.
I thought you were mistaken.
I thought you were from Osaka.
I'm wrong.
I've been reflecting on it for about two years.
I thought you were Hyogo, but I thought you were Osaka.
I didn't remember properly.
I'm sweating more than I did yesterday.
You sweat fast.
I'm from Hyogo.
I'm in Osaka now.
I'm outside of Kansai.
I'm glad.
I was full of energy.
There were a lot of people.
We said a lot.
But really, this...
What was it?
The name of Yoko...
Ikezono Yuri.
Ikezono-chan.
It's like, Yoko's mom.
It's really full of curiosity.
Like a true mom.
Everyone was like, yay!
It was really Yoko.
It was perfect.
But...
This broadcast was the last one.
The broadcast was the last one?
The broadcast was the last one.
Everyone is doing their best.
Thank you very much.
We still have the report on the school trip, so let's check it out.
Kumi-san, Nao-san, Haruo-san, hello.
I'm in Sendai now.
The stage performance in Sendai is over.
It was really fun to have a lot of people come.
Thank you very much.
And here is my school trip report.
Gyutan and Zunno-shiku.
I'm happy.
Then I would like to eat.
I will eat.
It's really delicious.
It's delicious.
Gyutan is a very chewy food, right?
Yes, it is.
It's chewy but very soft.
Even though it's a bento.
It's delicious.
Sendai's gyutan is the best.
Next, I'll have Zunda shake.
Let's eat.
It's delicious. I love Zunda shake.
I came to Sendai with Konishi, and I drank two glasses at that time.
I love it so much that I'm happy to drink it again this time.
I was able to do a lot of
I feel like I'm going to make it a huge success.
That's all from RIO Shimizu from Sendai.
Thank you.
That was a wonderful report.
Are we done?
No more.
It was a little bit of an incident.
What made you so excited?
Well...
It's okay.
It's okay?
I made a fuss.
Gyutan looked delicious.
It's delicious.
It's good to eat gyutan in Sendai.
Rio, don't you have anything?
I haven't said anything.
I think everyone has this.
But I don't think it's made.
Are you sure?
I think you're definitely making it.
I'm not making it.
On the contrary, it's rare to have it.
Well, it's not spread.
I know.
Really?
Yes.
Can I say it?
Umapparu!
I was right.
Nao-chan, you have one, too, right?
No.
I don't have one.
You don't?
I've never made one.
Have you ever heard of it?
No.
I've never said it.
What about you, Kumi?
I want to ask you something.
What was it?
I was in Sendai and ate beef tongue.
Can you do it from there?
Suddenly?
Director.
I ate beef tongue.
Ku-mikakusho-ku.
That's it.
As expected.
Ku-mikakusho-ku?
Ku-mikakusho-ku.
I'm sure Nao-chan will do it someday.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
There's still more. Please watch the first video.
Gumi-san, Nao-san, Haruyo-san, and everyone watching the live stream.
I'm Honoka Hirao, playing Miyuki Hanasato.
I'm Kirairi Takeuchi, playing Miyo Tsujisaka.
We're done with the stage in Hiroshima.
I realized that ZENBOM TOKYO is being shown all over the country.
Today's topic is our school trip.
We're going to eat something delicious.
What is it?
Ready, set, go!
Ta-da!
What is this?
Hiroshima style okonomiyaki!
It smells good!
It's cute.
Let's eat!
It's so hot!
Is it good?
It's good.
Let's eat.
It's sweet.
Yes, it is.
The sauce is sweet.
This is...
Umaho!
Umaho is here!
Kyoichi's voice came out.
Kyoichi?
It's Kyoichi.
I'm glad.
I'm eating.
There's squid.
It's big.
It's good. It's crunchy.
It's good.
Let's eat slowly after this.
Please watch ZENBOW OF TOKYO!
Thank you.
It looks so good.
Hiroshima is good.
Hiroshima, yes.
There is Okonomiyaki from Hiroshima.
That's right.
I want to eat it.
I think you'll be super excited about Okonomiyaki on your school trip.
I'll be like, let's go!
You'll be like, ahhh!
I think I will.
I'll be like, I'm so sad.
I'm so sad.
That's nice.
I don't like it in my hometown.
Do people in your hometown eat it?
I wonder.
Do they make it at home?
Do they have a grill?
But okonomiyaki and takoyaki are not for eating outside.
Oh, really?
They're for eating at home.
So Hiroshima people are like that too.
Let's ask Hirari again.
So amame is different from home.
It depends on the household.
I'm a little confused.
I'll listen to it.
I've thought about it.
It's good.
I'm glad everyone enjoyed it.
I'm glad.
It was fun.
It's the best to have fun.
Today, four students are having a stage greeting in seven cities nationwide.
Tomorrow, on the 26th, we will have a stage greeting at a theater in Tokyo.
Oh, they're separated.
It's like this.
The director is here too.
The director is here.
I thought it was only the members.
So they split it into three parts.
I guess that's what it is.
It seems like that.
I think we can hear a lot of stories.
Certainly.
Is this also after watching it?
Wait, what?
Three?
Four!
I got it!
It's this!
The second one is that Moriya-kun.
Moriya-kun is the director.
Director.
They're taking each other.
This is fun.
I want to go to all of them.
This is crazy.
I want to go to them after watching this.
I want to go to them.
I want to go to them today.
Wow, it looks so fun.
Everyone is going to the concert today, but we'll run and come back.
Run to Tokyo.
Run to Tokyo and come back and perform in Tokyo tomorrow.
It's the second day of the concert.
But many people will watch it.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
We still have time here.
Is that okay?
Let's go!
Good!
I'm really looking forward to it.
I love AXTER.
I can carry AXTER with me.
Let's all go to Tokyo together.
I'll carry it to the stadium.
Who is it?
There is a person.
Again?
I think...
She's saying shiii!
Don't say it!
I feel like I'm going to get a lot of things.
Ready?
Ah!
Chisa-chan!
Su-chan, again!
Oh, isn't this your first time?
Wakana-chan?
Yes
Cute
It's good
And?
I'm Mio-chan
Mio-chan
And Wakana-chan
Wakana-chan
Su-chan
Cute
Her forehead is nice
It's really cute
It suits her
Cute
It's amazing
It's nice
Cute
It's really cute
This is really nice
I want to put this on the outer frame
Right? Should we assemble it?
Yeah, let's do that.
Let's assemble it.
I only have Sutan and Settachan.
Isn't that amazing?
They're so strong.
Not that much.
No.
Oh!
So cute!
This size is perfect.
Which one is which?
Is there such a thing?
I did this
But I think there are some
This way?
Is it like this?
Everyone is the same
Mio-chan
I'm in Hiroshima
Hello
It's out
Cute
This is cute
This is really good
It's cute
The uniform is really good
It's super good
Cute!
There's a small one
This is...
Let's open it
It's really good
I love it
You can put it on a bookshelf
It's on display, isn't it?
I have a lot on display
I like it
Wait, it's an idol version
What?
Is this good?
This is good
This is good?
Is that okay?
That means it's okay.
It's a dream.
I'm wearing the same uniform as Alirin.
That's right.
Amazing.
Haru Haru's.
Moe-chan.
It's Moe-chan.
And...
Here it is.
Mastani-san.
I've been out with this Mastani-san.
What?
Really?
This pink...
Pink...
Pink inner Mastani-san.
It says on the schedule,
don't miss it.
What? Me?
No, no.
What are you talking about?
Don't say that.
Like...
Nani-san, Honishi said,
don't miss it.
I didn't say that.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sweating.
I'm sorry, my words were too much.
You're over-conscious.
No, my words were too much.
You're sweating more than yesterday.
Again?
I'm sweating again.
So, when you're shooting, you don't know what kind of clothes you're wearing.
And on the whole schedule, it says,
Don't take an exte for Konishi.
What does that mean?
Yes, that day.
It happened.
It's rare.
I ate omurice with this girl.
Cute.
This is Haruharu's X-T.
Yes.
Haruka probably wore it.
Always.
I don't wear it.
I did a video of saying, please don't take it off.
Oh, there was?
I only saw Hakonishi's.
Oh, cute.
So cute.
Idol Tsu-chan.
Can I see this?
It's Tsu-chan's dream.
It's a delusion.
It might be a delusion axe.
Cute.
I want to line them all up.
So cute.
I want to see this.
This is a character card.
Character card.
What character? Random character card.
There are a lot of randoms.
Random is fun.
Excuse me.
What kind of card is it?
It's pretty big.
It's a hand.
It depends on the person.
It's a hand for someone.
It's my hand.
It's a postcard.
Did you see it?
Why?
Kumi-san?
Let's go.
Ready, set, go.
Oh!
Cute!
That's right.
Oh, it's Master Ni again.
Master Ni-san.
Me-gu-chan.
Thank you.
First Me-gu-chan.
Ikezono-san.
Amazing.
Cute.
It's a face when I'm looking at Moriya.
It's Ikezono-san.
Amazing.
Cute.
This is really good.
This is a camera.
This is what Yoko is drawing.
Yes.
The schedule is also behind.
Oh, it's true.
The characters are also Yoko's.
Oh, is it different?
I wonder what it is.
It's like that.
I feel like it's Yoko's.
This Yoko is good.
This is probably when she's all alone.
She's having fun alone.
She's having fun.
She's smiling.
This Kaho Rin has sparkling eyes.
It's so cute.
It's true.
It's cute.
When Moriya is watching.
She's looking at us.
That's the scene.
I know that scene.
Maybe the viewers will understand.
This is good.
Is this a
It's like a
I feel like that.
It's true.
I'm curious. It's true. It's like a rainbow.
I'll open it. Thank you.
I'm happy to open it so randomly.
It's cute. Pink. Chisa-chan.
Chisa-chan. It's a rainbow color.
It's nice.
Is this...
Ikesono-han?
Is that so?
Isn't it amazing?
Is it a coincidence?
Is this a coincidence?
Amazing!
Isn't this amazing?
It's pretty...
It's really without any decorations.
It's the first half...
The half of the half before the half.
Amazing!
Decorations?
Isn't this amazing?
It's a coincidence.
Amazing.
I'm surprised I noticed.
I thought it was me.
Amazing.
This is amazing.
Randomly, the first time we went like this with these 5 people
I wonder if it's true
It's not
Amazing
It's amazing
There is such a way to enjoy
Certainly, it's good to line up like this
Line up like this
It's good
There are various ways to enjoy
There is
Yes
Yoko finished her stage performance and the last video was uploaded.
Please watch it.
Kumi-san, Rao-san, Haruo-san.
Thank you for the broadcast.
I'm Yoko Shouken, the voice of Yurika Ikeda.
Thank you for your cooperation.
This is the last episode of the school trip.
I think there are members from all over the country, but I am from Osaka.
Everyone, I think you remember this place.
The correct answer is Glico.
This is my first time here.
This is Ebisu Bridge.
I'm glad I came here for the first time.
I've always wanted to come here.
This is a famous place.
There are many fashion shops.
And I can smell the good smell from the surrounding.
I can smell the delicious takoyaki.
And I can smell the good smell.
I can smell the good smell.
I feel like I'm in the city.
I'm from Osaka, so I'm close to the city.
I often go to Umeda in Osaka, but I'm glad I came here for the first time.
It says crab in the back.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
Yes.
It's already very busy.
As it was last week, there were many foreign tourists.
I would like to be able to get on the plane with the voice of the foreign tourists.
I think it's okay so far.
I look forward to your continued support.
Please watch the movie.
I'm looking forward to your impressions.
What are you doing?
What?
Uriko!
Cute!
I wonder if she will do it.
I thought it was a little bit, but I was left at the end.
cute
It's so cute.
What is it?
Yoko Osaka's Glico.
Is it a child?
I got a report from Yoko Osaka.
It was bright.
Osaka still
Yes
isses
It's a little cringe when angry like that.
It's a parallel world.
I think it's because we're running away.
It's a city where you can't sleep.
I see.
I heard that you were called by an overseas person.
There was such a scene.
I was left in my heart there.
What was it?
I wonder what it was.
I couldn't think of the scene.
It was a scene with a foreigner.
I wanted to see it again.
Please watch it.
I didn't think of it.
I only thought it was cute.
I will think of it next time.
I was wondering what it meant.
That's what I was thinking.
So I wanted to watch it again.
I'll watch it.
Please pay attention to that.
Please.
So,
we went to many places.
Is there a place you want to go?
If we go on a school trip together,
where would you go?
Anywhere?
Anywhere.
県ですか? 都道府県? 日本で。 I'm from Japan.
どこでもいいよ。日本じゃなくて。 Anywhere is fine.
決めました。 早いね。 決めました? 決めてない。 もう決めてない。
なんでですか? これ生配信か? 考えてたのよ。 全然決めてない。
でも、まあ。 But...
Oh, I've decided.
Really?
It looks like you haven't decided.
I'll ask you.
Me?
There's a possibility that you'll choose.
Hokkaido?
Wait, Hokkaido.
I like Hokkaido too.
Let's go to Hokkaido.
I want to go. I want to have Kaho-rin do a lot of things.
I want to go to Otaru.
Oh, I see.
I've never been to Otaru.
I've never been anywhere.
Hokkaido?
I've never been to Hokkaido.
I've never been to the top of the mountain, more than Sendai.
I see, the one in Tohoku.
I've never been to Tohoku.
Let's go.
Let's go to Iwate.
At the event.
Isn't it private?
No, it's not.
Let's go.
We can go to Hokkaido right away.
You always say that.
I think Kumi can go anywhere.
Even if it's beyond Japan.
It's about two hours by plane.
It's about this long.
I can go there right away.
If it's about three nights.
It's like a huge Harappa.
Everyone is like...
Pull the blue sheet.
Blue sheet?
It's a leisure sheet.
Blue sheet limited.
It's good.
Because it's big.
Because it's big and strong.
It's like sky blue.
Yeah, it's sky blue.
It's sunny.
I want to make it double.
It's a little bit like a summer vacation.
The place where you take a full sheet.
Yes.
Let's go together.
Let's go to the square.
Yes.
I got the image.
Don't stick it in the blue sheet.
Nao stuck it in the blue sheet.
I imagined it.
We all drew the blue sheet and imagined playing with it.
I can't do it.
I'll definitely bring a blue sheet.
That's it for today.
How was the live stream?
Let's read the comments.
I really want you to watch the movie.
Please watch it.
It's a youthful movie.
This is the first scene that I can't say.
It's like a school trip.
Everyone is sitting.
I love that scene!
I know.
I was looking for the four-year-old.
Where is she?
I know.
There was something like this.
It's good in the bus.
That's right.
I was so confused.
I like the youth.
It's good.
It's not my comment.
It's not a blue sheet.
It's a blue sheet.
It's a story of a stage greeting.
There are a lot of goods.
I'm hungry.
I ate a lot.
I ate a lot of rice.
I want to eat grilled fish.
I ate a dumpling.
I was eaten by a dumpling.
I'll eat it when I get home.
I had a school trip today.
What?
Where did the shoulder go?
Did it come back?
Oh, but it's the current season. It's October.
That's right.
There are a lot of people.
Then it's really good, isn't it?
What?
It's really good.
It's like you remember.
I remember.
It's amazing.
It's good.
It's far away.
I see.
It's good.
What?
Hmm.
I want to hear about your memories of school trips.
I want to hear a lot.
Let's do a live stream like that.
Let's ask questions.
I want to hear about everyone's stories.
I'm going to go see it tomorrow.
There are many.
I'll show you my shoes.
There are many more.
There are many goods.
There are many.
I'll take this home.
All of them.
My notebook.
Notebook.
It's Australian.
There's a notebook.
Please open this by yourself.
It's nice.
Everyone wants to watch it live.
I want to watch it again.
When we talk together, we talk about how it was.
I want to watch that scene again.
I've been thinking about it.
I know.
So that's why I'm here.
I want to see more details.
Please watch it.
It's a really fun movie full of the charms of the four-year-olds.
So please watch it at the ZENBOU of TOKYO theater.
Thank you.
So, thank you to all the four-year-olds.
Thank you for watching the delivery.
See you again.
Goodbye.
Web of Tokyo.
Please watch it.
Bye bye.